{
    "subject": "resource/Holy_Roman_Empire",
    "predicate": "property/continent",
    "object": "Europe",
    "human_readable": "The Holy Roman Empire is located in Europe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9657031297683716,
            "question": "Was the Holy Roman Empire part of Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9176949262619019,
            "question": "Is Europe home to the Holy Roman Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9008919596672058,
            "question": "Where was the Holy Roman Empire located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5808644890785217,
            "question": "What continent was the Holy Roman Empire on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5367149114608765,
            "question": "What continent is known for containing the Holy Roman Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39483577013015747,
            "question": "Is the Holy Roman Empire in Asia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36188095808029175,
            "question": "In which direction from Asia would you find the Holy Roman Empire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32638293504714966,
            "question": "Is the Holy Roman Empire located in South America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28047096729278564,
            "question": "Could you find the Holy Roman Empire in North America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23009620606899261,
            "question": "If someone traveled to Africa, would they be in the Holy Roman Empire?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Holy Roman Empire is located in Europe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6942_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Could you find the Holy Roman Empire in North America?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6942_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the Holy Roman Empire located in South America?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6942_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which direction from Asia would you find the Holy Roman Empire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6942_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6942_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms the Holy Roman Empire existed in Central Europe during the Middle Ages and the early modern period, which is a subset of Europe. The fact that it encompassed territories across present-day Germany, Switzerland, Liechtenstein, Luxembourg, Czech Republic, Austria, Slovenia, Belgium, and the Netherlands, as well as parts of France, Italy, Poland, Croatia, Belgium, and the Netherlands, further supports this conclusion."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about the geographical context of the Holy Roman Empire, stating that it encompassed territories in Central Europe and neighboring regions. This supports the statement that \"The Holy Roman Empire is located in Europe.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}